pokemonromhack.com 2019-05-19

# Website Privacy Policy - Pokemon ROM Hacks

**Privacy Policy for pokemonromhack.com**

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to [contact us](https://pokemonromhack.com/contact-us).

At pokemonromhack.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by pokemonromhack.com and how it is used.

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, pokemonromhack.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
pokemonromhack.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

**Advertising and Analytics Services Provided by Others**

We may allow others to provide analytics services and serve advertisements on our behalf across the internet and in applications. These entities may use cookies, web beacons, device identifiers and other technologies to collect information about your use of the Services and other websites and applications, including your IP address, web browser, mobile network information, pages viewed, time spent on pages or in apps, links clicked and conversion information. This information may be used by PokemonROMHack.com and others to, among other things, analyze and track data, determine the popularity of certain content, deliver advertising and content targeted to your interests on our Services and other websites and better understand your online activity. For a full list of the companies we partner with to show you interest-based ads, please visit <https://pokemonromhack.com/partner-opt-out>. For more information about interest-based ads, or to opt out of having your web browsing information used for interest-based advertising purposes, please visit [www.aboutads.info/choices](http://www.aboutads.info/choices). Your device may also include a feature (“Limit Ad Tracking” on iOS or “Opt Out of Interest-Based Ads” or “Opt Out of Ads Personalization” on Android) that allows you to opt out of having certain information collected through apps used for interest-based advertising purposes.

pokemonromhack.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. pokemonromhack.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.
